(This time, they're taking a picture of LOOΠΔ full group in order of each units!)
'LOOΠΔ1/3, stand here!'
'And please stand there, yyxy'
YeoJin: (What about me?)
'Okay, you stand in the middle!'
YeoJin: (Okay!)
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ - Hi High"
(Finally, the photo shooting as a full group is over!)
Kim Lip: The 3-day-long photo shooting is over finally!
HeeJin: To be honest, It wasn't hard at all because we did it altogether!
HeeJin: Instaed of that, it was super fun!
HaSeul: A little while ago, HeeJin told me that it's like visiting relatives~
HeeJin: Right~ It feels like I'm in grandparents' house in holidays~
YeoJin: We're practicing so hard and trying our best to show you a better LOOΠΔ
YeoJin: So please look forward to us!
(And please look forward to the upcoming episodes of LOOΠΔ TV for a music video shooting, too!)